transfirst.com 2012-10-05

# TransFirst Privacy Policy

Home Privacy Policy

## TransFirst® Privacy Policy

At TRANSFIRST, and our affiliated companies, we greatly appreciate the opportunity to serve our customers. We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of our potential, current and former customers' information. The information obtained will be used solely for the purpose of providing the services mutually agreed upon. This information will be protected with industry-standard technical safeguards and will adhere to applicable standards and requirements as set forth by the relevant governing bodies. 

When you visit our website, you can do so without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. The only information we collect is that which you provide voluntarily. This information may include, for example, name, company name, e-mail address and phone number. We would use this information only to respond with information you have requested, such as program details or pricing, or to follow up on job opportunities you have asked about. 

If you elect to provide us with your information, then any data you specifically and knowingly provide will become the property of TRANSFIRST. This also applies if you send us email. However, TRANSFIRST is committed to protecting the privacy of any personal information you give us.

We do not release any customer information to outside independent telemarketing or direct mail marketing firms. Customer information is shared with our affiliate companies, outside vendors and/or parties only when disclosure of such information is necessary to complete account set-up, process bankcard transactions, and to perform such services as are requested by you or when applicable law or legal authority requires that such information be disclosed.

TRANSFIRST has established physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect our customer's privacy. One of the ways we protect our customer information is by limiting access to information to those employees who have a business reason to access the information. In addition, we train our employees about the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of customer information. We take appropriate disciplinary action to enforce our employees' privacy responsibilities.

TRANSFIRST reserves the right to modify and update this privacy policy at any time. If you are concerned about use of your information, you may contact TRANSFIRST at 800-745-2659.
